原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译   千只鹤飞过波千鸟  tong大梨
翻译   A序列  屯栗子  马丁马丁回音山
翻译   AlgerDestiny  不见  VC
校对     屯栗子
时间轴     兜兜兜爹
后期     渔夫
总监     屯栗子
辛普森一家
第三十一季  第十七集
超前教育中心
来吧  阿麦
Come on, Maggie.
你好  不好意思我们迟到了
Hi. Sorry we're late.
这是阿麦  我们第一次来
This is Maggie. We're here for our first day.
你好阿麦  之后谁来接呢
Hello, Maggie. And who will be picking her up?
什么  她倒下之后吗
W-- A-After she falls down?
不是  放学之后
No, at the end of the day.
慢着  我不能陪读吗
Wait, I don't stay with her?
研究表明超前儿童
Research shows pre-toddlers learn best
在没有家长在场的情况下学得最好
in a parent-free environment.
除非你想阻碍她成长  那也很好
Unless you want to stunt her growth, which is great.
我们不能评判的
We're not supposed to judge.
不不  不是这样的
No, no, it's not that.
我只是不想阿麦觉得自己被抛弃了
I just don't want Maggie to feel abandoned.
那四点见了
So, we'll see you at 4:00.
好吧
Oh. Okay, then.
今天接下来我该干什么呢
Hmm. Now what will I do with the rest of my day
我知道了  我问问最爱的妈咪博客
I know. I'll ask my favorite mommy blog.
这就对了妈咪
照顾好你自己
上一节动感单车课吧
老妹儿
现在把阻力加到最大
Now turn that resistance all the way up!
加把劲  我想看你们这帮臭女人受苦受累
Come on! I want to see you bitches suffer!
难道只有我一个人听到这句话了
Am I the only one who heard that?
我爱死了
I love it.
就好像听着脑海里的声音接受训练
It's like being coached by the voice inside my head.
往死里练  你们这群活在陆地上的海牛
Spin yourselves to death, you land manatees!
用陶艺来表达你一无是处的自我吧
卖力画  长着香肠手指的没用东西
Paint harder, you sausage-fingered no-talents!
给你工作中的男人一个香艳惊喜
"给你工作中的男人一个香艳惊喜"
"Sex-prise your man at work."
你来干嘛
What are you doing here?
也许你可以给我来个安全检查
Maybe you could give me a safety inspection.
我的天  我真是不敢相信
Oh, my God, I can't believe this is happening.
我完全被香艳惊喜到了
I'm so sex-prised!
这里到处都有摄像头
There's security cameras everywhere,
所以我们得偷偷地躲在桌子下
so we'll have to snuggle under the desk.
请直接在桌子上
On top of the desk, please.
谢了杰瑞  干得真漂亮
Thanks, Jerry! Nice. Real cool.
现在我该怎么打发时间
Now how do I fill the day? Hmm.
很好&非常好
正在招聘
什么是很好加非常好
What's Well Plus Good?
应该念很好&非常好
It's pronounced "Well and Good."
怎么每个人都在跟我说话
Ugh, why is everyone talking to me?
如果这些人都想在这里工作
Well, if all these people want to work here,
也许我也想在这里工作
maybe I want to work here.
很好&非常好  正在招聘
去七号平板那里
All right, go to tablet seven
拿你的预申请道德评价表
to take your pre-application ethics assessment.
顺便  头发挺酷
Cool hair, by the way.
你觉得我头发很酷
You think that my hair is cool?
谢谢  劳伦
Well, thank you, Lauren.
顺便  你的名牌颠倒了
Oh, by the way, your name tag is upside down.
谢谢
Mm, thank you.
你是唯一一个注意到的人
You're the only person to mention that.
妈妈的气场  她简直完美
Major mom vibes. She's perfect.
我永远不会撒谎
"I always never lie."
预申请道德评估
"我从不撒谎"
1)总是
2)有时
3)从不
选二  我有时从不撒谎
Two. "I sometimes always never lie."
预申请道德评估
如果我从未找到一个钱包  我一定会还回去
1)总是
2)从不
3)以上一些
4)总是从不
如果我从未找到一个钱包  我一定会还回去
"If I never found a wallet, I would always give it back."
这钱包是什么颜色的
What color is the wallet?
马姬·辛普森  其实并没有什么测试
Marge Simpson. There was never a test.
除非这一直都是测试
Except there always was.
-没有吗  -而且你通过了
- There wasn't? - And you passed.
欢迎来到很好&非常好大家庭
Welcome to the Well and Good family.
其他人可以走了  你们的简历将被删除
The rest of you can go. Your résumés will be deleted.
我是你们唯一雇用的人吗
I'm the only one you hired?
你是唯一一个和我们合伙的人
You're the only one we partnered with.
很好&非常好
盛大开幕
好了  现在我在这工作了
Okay, so I work here now.
还没问我们卖什么
I never asked what we sell.
我可以搞清楚
I can figure this out.
糖果  爆炸浴盐  喷灯
Candy? Bath bombs? Blowtorches?
30块一瓶的苏打水
$30 bottles of soda?
不好意思
Excuse me.
你建议我买酊剂还是油
Do you recommend the tincture or the oil?
我...我猜酊剂可能更贵吧
I-- the-the tincture is more expensive, I guess.
这事关你自己
Look, this is about you.
我觉得  要照顾好你自己
And taking care of you. I think.
所以你要把自己...放在第一位
So you have to put yourself... first?
你朴实无华略显笨拙的销售策略
Well, your no-frills, fumbling sales pitch
已经打动了我  我两种都买
has won me over. I'll take both. Yes...
姑娘  你刚刚卖出了一百块
Wow, girl, you just made a hundred-dollar sale.
你一定非常适合这里
You're gonna fit in great here.
问题是  这里卖什么
Thing is, what does here sell?
现在要玩RadioShack那一套吗
Is this what RadioShack is now?
不  我们是一家高端大麻精品店
No. We're a high-end cannabis boutique.
你们卖大麻
You sell pot?!
准确地说  我负责检查身份证
Technically, I check I.D.s.
你卖大麻
You sell pot.
我是个毒贩子
I'm a drugs dealer!
现在在本州  大麻已经合法了
Cannabis is legal in this state now.
水橇也合法
Well, so is water-skiing,
但这并不意味着我就要去卖它
but that doesn't mean I have to sell it!
抱歉
I'm sorry.
马姬  不要离开  我是认真的
Marge, don't leave, seriously.
我请求你
Like, I'm asking.
德里克·塔图姆  我有你的台面式烤架
Drederick Tatum! I own your countertop grill.
尽量不要在不粘表面上使用金属器具
Take care not to use metal utensils on the non-stick surfaces.
但是  在我的拳击生涯结束之后
But anyway, after my boxing career ended,
我非常痛苦
I was in a lot of pain.
具体地讲  痛在我出拳的手
Specifically, in my punching hands
还有我被拳击的脸
and my blocking face.
但是服用了大麻油
But following a regimen of CBD oil
以及皮卡丘烟枪的药效
and medicinal hits from a Pikachu bong,
我又能够享受生活了
I was able to enjoy life again.
因此激励了我创立了很好&非常好康复商场
Which inspired me to create Well and Good Healing Emporiums.
电影里的切齐和钟才吸大麻呢
But pot is for Cheeches... and Chongs.
马姬  这不是为了爽
Marge, it's not about getting high.
这关系到人们的身心健康
It's about wellness.
这就是为什么我在这里聘用了优秀的团队
And that's why I've hand-picked the perfect team here.
我是大麻成分和最新配售系统的专家
I'm an expert in cannabinoids and cutting-edge delivery systems,
又叫浸煮器  脱羧基  皮下吸收和宠物栓剂
aka infusers, decarboxylators, transdermals and pet suppositories.
而我很性感
And I'm super hot.
你们要我做什么
And what do you need me for?
马姬  大家知道你想伸出援手  这里很安全
Marge, people know you want to help them, that it's safe here.
1980年上映的美国喜剧电影
你之前说  不像《喜剧二人组》里的情节
Not some place for Cheeches and Chongs, as you so recently put it.
非常抱歉  我不认为这是真实的自我
Uh, I'm sorry. I don't think this is really me.
祝你的生活方式好运
Good luck with your lifestyle.
没有治疗感情受伤的药物真遗憾
Oh, it's a shame there's no drug for hurt feelings.
在这里呢
Oh, wait, there totally is.
伤感情药品
你知道吗  在一些家庭里他们围坐在一起
You know, in some families, they go around the table
每人都要说一件当天的见闻
and everyone says one thing they learned that day.
我知道了这个
Okay. I learned that.
我知道了前重量级拳击手世界冠军
Well, I learned that the former heavyweight champion
拥有一家大麻商店
of the world owns a marijuana store.
他提供给我一份工作  被我回绝了
And he offered me a job, which I turned down.
等下  什么
Wait, what?
这些人真的很优秀
I mean, the people were really cool,
他们认为我很优秀
and they thought I was cool,
这让我感觉很振奋
which made me feel "Stoked."
但是我不想成为一名大麻销售员
But I'm not going to be a reefer saleslady.
我认为这没什么不妥的
Well, I guess there's nothing wrong with it.
在这个州大麻是合法的
Cannabis is legal in this state.
这和你在卖酒的地方工作没什么两样
Yeah, it's basically the same thing as working in a liquor store.
你能在卖酒的地方工作吗
You can work in a liquor store?
别做梦了  伙计
Stay with us, big guy.
我以为你们会反对这件事
Wow. I thought you'd be opposed to it.
现如今人们压力很大
People are stressed out these days.
坏血病卷土重来  世界战火纷飞
Scurvy is back, there's, like, 60 wars going on.
鲸鱼正在吃掉我们宝贵的海洋塑料
Whales are eating our precious ocean plastic.
也许人们需要一根大麻烟
Maybe people want to smoke a doob for that.
是啊  现在所有人都把垃圾卖给瘾君子
Oh, yeah, everyone's selling crap to stoners now.
你看过阿壳汉堡店的广告了吗
Have you seen the new Krusty Burger commercial?
此处也指吸毒之后的饥饿感
出于某种原因  当你找到零食的时候
When you've got the munchies, for some reason--
你那极度渴望的眼神
wink, wink-- you crave weird.
油炸牛肋排配上热乎的甜甜圈
A deep-fried rib-wich served on a warm doughnut.
还有意大利面夹心的奶酪三明治
Or a spaghetti-filled grilled cheese sandwich
淋上农场布丁
drizzled with ranch pudding.
阿壳能让您大饱口福
Krusty's Munchie Mouthfuls.
是时候来尝尝了
It's high time you tried it.
你懂了吗  懂了吗
Get it? Get it?!
懂了吗
Get it?
我懂了
I get it.
塔图姆先生亲自选了我
Well, Mr. Tatum did personally choose me.
他说我很乐于助人
He said I was helpful.
亲爱的  你是我见过最喜欢帮忙的人
Honey, you're the most helpful person I've ever met.
去卖那合法安全的毒品吧
Now go sell the safe legal drugs
当然孩子们绝对不能碰
our kids should never, ever use!
尤其是巴仔
Especially Bart!
很好&非常好康复商场
大麻软糖
这是个苹果零售店吗
Is this an Apple store?
进来的每个人都这么问
Everyone keeps asking that.
我关节炎发作  把手机摔地上了
I dropped my phone because of my arthritis.
我们不修手机
We can't fix your phone,
但我可以帮你缓解关节炎
but I can sure help with that arthritis.
试试这瓶神奇止痛乳液
Try this amazing pain-relieving lotion.
有些刺痛
Oh. It tingles.
和采婷牌不一样  我恨采婷
Not like Jergens. I hate Jergens!
你看起来压力很大
You seem stressed. Hmm.
要来点儿美味软糖吗
Why not try some yummy gummies?
很好&非常好康复商场
马姬  谢谢你
Marge, thank you.
母亲大人开心了  我也开心
When Mother's happy, I'm happy.
或者说  至少没那么惨了
Or at least, much less miserable.
这个大人物可是一整所学校的校长
This big shot here is the principal of a whole school!
给她秀秀你的钥匙串
Show her your key ring.
爱了爱了
Oh, I love it.
我想来点大麻
Psst. I want to buy some pot.
别急别急  短裤仔
All right, pump the brakes, Jhorts.
我得先问你几个问题
Got to ask a few questions first.
你是想全身麻
Now, do you want a body high
还是就脸上麻一点
or a front-of-the-face buzz?
无所谓  随便哪个都行
I don't know. Just hook me up.
我知道你想要什么了
Mmm, I have the perfect strain in mind.
但悠着点用
But be warned, boo,
用了这款你整个人会瘫掉起不来
the couch-lock is strong on this one,
但优点是不会有记忆丢失
but there's, like, zero mind earse.
你在扯什么  我只是想要点...
W-What are you saying? I just want...
大麻
weed.
别急  马上就好  听我说完
Okay, almost there. Almost there. Now listen.
你是想要大麻粉末
Do you want this in flour...
浓缩液  还是外用的
...shatter, topical...
内服的  还是鼻喷雾剂
...edible, nasal mist...
滴耳剂
...ear drops?
我只是想从一个不管是不是警察的人手上
Look, I just want to score a bag of shwag
买一袋最普通的大麻
from some dude who may or may not be a cop.
我是个警察
I'm a cop.
你试过这个吗
Have you tried this?
这一切都说不通了
Nothing makes sense anymore!
给我瓶啤酒
Give me a beer.
啤酒不会让我的头发有烟味儿
It doesn't make my hair smell like anything!
我一辈子都盼望着大麻合法化
I dreamed my whole life of legalized weed.
结果原来这么扫兴
Turns out it's a real buzzkill.
可不是嘛
Ain't that the truth?
时代变了
Times have changed.
酒精带来的浪漫感已经逐渐消逝了
The romance of alcohol is fading into the past.
瘾君子们永远不会知道坐在马桶上
Stoners will never know the joy of sitting on the toilet
然后吐到自己内裤里的乐趣
and barfing into your own underwear.
或者是和比你壮两倍的人打架
Or picking a fight with a guy twice your size
因为他走路蹭到你的车了
because his leg touched your car.
我也怀念过去的日子
Yeah. I miss the old days, too.
那时候找大麻...又阴暗又艰难
When buying pot was... scuzzy.
为了回到过去  我愿意付出任何代价
I'd pay anything to turn back that clock.
你知道现在什么会受欢迎吗
You know what'd be popular?
如果这些合法的地方
If one of those legal places
能打造成好像在通过以前学校老关系
made it feel like you were scoring weed
偷偷吸毒品的感觉
from your old-school pot connection.
这个主意很棒  我们应该这么做
That's a great idea, and we should do it.
那些老烟枪们
Those tie-dyed bong monkeys
会为这些玩意付出大价钱
will cough up big-time for the full dirtbag shebang!
我去告诉那些老烟枪们
I'll alert the bong monkeys.
绅士们下午好  来点泡沫吗
Afternoon, gernts. You need some suds?
达夫超人知道大家需要达夫啤酒提神醒脑
Duffman knows it's always time for a refreshing Duff!
没错  我们听说
Yeah, that being said,
巴里有时候也想找点草药类提神醒脑的东西
sometimes Barry is looking for a little herbal refreshment.
懂我意思吗
Know what I mean?
这边  各位
Right this way, fellas.
你们是老谋子的朋友吗
So you guys friends of Moe?
对  他们很酷
Yeah. Uh, these guys are cool.
厉害  各位绅士们请进
Whoa, tight. Come on in, gentlemen.
等等  有个免责声明
Oh, wait. Here's a disclaimer, man.
这里是一个合法药房
"This is a legal dispensary,
遵循所有法律法规
"Compliant with all laws and statutes.
作为体验的一部分
"As part of the experience,
演员们会假装这些事是不合法的
cast members may pretend it's illegal."
好吧  开始吗
All right. Shall we?
疯狂的鸟  生锈的杠铃
Hmm. Crazy bird, rusty free weights,
所有东西闻上去都像湿乎乎的泳衣霉味
everything smells like a damp swimsuit...
我到家了
I'm home.
你演的是谁
Who are you supposed to be?
从不认可你的怪朋友
I'm the weird friend who never acknowledges you.
我以前是这么对待老室友斯考特的
I was that guy for my old roommate Scott.
放在邦迪的盒子里就行
Just stick it in the Band-Aid can.
这都是根茎和种子
Wh-- It's all stems and seeds.
谢谢
Thank you.
生意兴隆  冠军让嗨变得高端
n微软雅黑s20\3c&000000&\bord1《奢侈时报》
龌龊的体验
n微软雅黑s20\3c&000000&\bord120世纪福斯[有造假意]
我同意付款  船长
n微软雅黑s20\3c&000000&\bord1很好&非常好品牌
n微软雅黑s20\3c&000000&\bord1邦迪盒
我同意付款  拉尔戈
n微软雅黑s20\3c&000000&\bord1很好&非常好品牌
我同意付款  肯特·布罗克曼
那么  鉴于很好&非常好品牌的成功
So, with the success of the Well and Good brand
真的  谢天谢地
which, you know, thank God--
我非常高兴向大家展示最新的风投
I'm so pleased to present our latest venture...
这就是大名鼎鼎的德里克豪宅
This is The Drederick.
一个完全合法的大麻度假spa圣地
It's a fully realized cannabis resort and spa.
我们的午餐活动
Now, for our launch event,
将会邀请大麻界的知名人士  从戴夫·夏佩尔
we'll be inviting marijuana influencers from Dave Chapelle
到哈里森·福特  他正在放飞自我
to Harrison Ford, who is flying himself, by the way,
所以请各位祈祷
so you know, fingers crossed.
马姬  我在想由你来担任
Marge, I was thinking that you would be
午餐派对的主持人
the hostess of this launch party,
作为很好&非常好品牌的实际代言人
acting as the de facto face of the Well and Good brand.
天哪  为何是我
Oh, my God. Why me?
马姬  因为大家信任你
Well, Marge, 'cause people trust you.
而且我的脸是创造了
Also, my face is the intellectual property
这个纹身的艺术家的知识产权
of the artist who created this tattoo.
所以你知道  我不能露面
So, you know, I'm out.
我很愿意
Oh, I'd love to.
太叫人激动了
This is so exciting, I...
等下  不是的  我是想请你的
Wait, wait, no. I wanted to ask you.
但不幸的是  大麻这事有个煞风景的人
But unfortunately, there was a fly in the CBD ointment.
你的丈夫侯默在卖大麻  马姬
Your husband Homer is selling weed, Marge.
太可怕了
That's terrible.
等下  我也是  我们都在卖
Wait, no, so am I. We all are.
我们在努力美化大麻制品的形象
We are trying to elevate the image of cannabis.
而这是他干的事
This is what he's doing.
他知道我靠卖大麻提高了多少自尊心
Oh, he knows how much self-esteem I get from selling bud.
那是我们的好飞盘
And that's our good frisbee.
要是你丈夫把大麻带回2018年的黑暗时刻
I'm afraid that you cannot continue with this company
恐怕你就没办法继续在这公司工作了
while your husband is taking pot back to the dark ages of 2018.
-我很抱歉  -不  不  不要
- I-I'm very sorry. - Oh, no. No, no, no.
请不要炒了我
Please, please don't fire me.
我想成为你们的门面
I want to be your face.
等侯默知道他这样有多伤害我
When Homer realizes how much this is hurting me,
我相信他会明白的
I'm sure he'll understand.
我不明白
I don't understand.
我们做的是一样的  顶多你穿得像医生
We're doing the same thing, except you dress like a doctor,
我穿得像是很酷的小孩
and I dress like a cool toddler.
你不懂吗
Don't you get it?
我是治愈者  你是致郁者
I'm a healer, and you're a dealer.
你得停手了
You need to quit.
我什么时候想停就停  我就不想
I can quit whenever I want. I just don't want to.
我嫁的你不是日常半途而废吗
What happened to the quitter I married?
我放弃半途而废了
I quit quitting!
-怎么回事  -妈妈爸爸在毒品战争
- What's going on? - Mom and Dad are having a drug war.
-有什么差别  -而且你花了一千块
- It's not different! - And you spent $1,000...
因为我  美国广播公司更有意思了
I make CNN much funnier!
《辛普森一家》曾预言特朗普当选总统
很好&非常好
大麻喷雾
侯默不肯放弃
Homer wouldn't quit.
这是我的工作服  大麻仓库的钥匙
Here's my smock, my key to the hash register,
写着合伙人的工牌
my business card reading "Associate."
我没法当公司的门面
Instead of being the face of the company,
我就只是我了
my face will just be me.
等下  马姬  还有个办法可以挽回工作
Wait, Marge. There is one way to save your job,
但是这样就要你背叛你的丈夫
but it would entail the betrayal of your husband,
我绝对不会要求你这么做的
which I would never ask you to do.
说说也无妨
Well, I mean, it doesn't hurt to ask.
只要有你帮忙  我们能让政府让他关门
With your help, we can get the government to shut him down.
联调局  缉毒局
The FBI? The DEA?
郡卫生局
The County Health Department.
马克的未标记租赁面包车
要是没标记  就是马克的
mark作为动词是标记的意思
卫生局
我没懂  侯默犯了什么罪
I don't understand. What crime is Homer committing?
大麻是合法的
Pot's legal.
没错  但他没有执照
Yes, but he isn't licensed to serve
不能提供非精神类的可食用物  即食物
non-psychotropic edibles, aka food.
如果他给了顾客零食  而他们
If he offers snacks to his customers and they eat
哪怕只吃了一口  我们就进去逮捕他
even one bite, we go in and take him down.
所以我们需要你进去  用这个下套
So we need you to bait the trap with these.
芝士球
你干吗
Are you in?
投中了
Nailed it.
你就是我从未有过的儿子
You're the son I never had.
侯默  看看谁来了
Hey, Homer. Look who's stopped by over here.
我很抱歉跟你吵架了
I am so sorry about our little tiff.
你会接受这份道歉礼  让你和朋友们分享吗
Will you accept this apology gift for you and your friends?
亲爱的  你总是站在我这边
Oh honey, you're always in my corner.
我有世上最深情  最支持我  最忠诚的妻子
I have the most loving, supportive, loyal wife in the world.
如果辛普森一直这么吃下去
If Simpson keeps eating like this,
还没等其他人上钩他就吃光了
he'll hit bottom dust before anyone takes the bait.
你这个死胖子  给你的顾客吃点芝士球
Come on, you fat bastard, offer the customer some cheese balls.
整层楼就是个气垫曲棍球桌
And the whole floor is an air hockey table,
搬动家具就像是...
so moving furniture, is like...
侯默  给你的朋友们吃点芝士球吧
Homer! Give your friends some cheese balls.
有人想来点吗
Would anyone care to partake?
-橙色警报  -快快快
- Code Orange. - Go, go, go!
别吃了
Stop eating!
我们是卫生部  这是突击检查
Health Department. This is a raid.
我们得丢掉这东西
We got to get rid of the stuff.
不要啊  快点
Oh, no! Come on!
老天
Oh, God!
证物
我们万事俱备了
We got everything we need.
你被勒令停业了  老兄
You're shut down, pal.
已封锁
你  你早就知道
You, you knew.
-你...  -给你设了圈套
- You... - Set you up.
跟我们走吧  混蛋  要交25美金的罚款
You're coming with us, scumbag, to pay a $25 fine.
德里克豪宅
发布会
马姬  亲爱的  一切都太完美了
Marge, darling, everything is so perfect.
但愿你丈夫不会太难过
I hope your husband wasn't too upset about the...
因为你的背叛
you know, the treachery.
侯默很好相处的  所以...
Oh well, Homer is very easygoing, so...
打扰一下  这些油性和粘性液体
Excuse me, can any of these oils or goos
能治疗我的刀伤吗
help me with a knife wound?
有人从背后捅了我一刀
I have been stabbed, in the back!
你怎么进来的  这里仅凭邀请入内
How did you get in? This is by invitation only.
我说我是凯文·史密斯的父亲
I said I was Kevin Smith's father.
美国导演  演员
没人质疑我
No one questioned me.
侯默  克制一下  你要惹恼那些影响者了
Homer, control yourself. You're upsetting the influencers.
他们很容易被影响
They're very easily influenced.
那家伙在喝酒
That guy is on alcohol.
请别破坏这事
Please don't ruin this.
这有关大麻健康公司生死  而我是公司的门面
This is cannabinoid health, and I am its face.
大妈健康吧
Cabana boy health.
如果它对你好处这么大
If it's so good for you...
那你为什么从不抽大麻
why have you never tried pot, ever?
医生需要亲自试试胰岛素
Well-- does a doctor need to try insulin
才知道它能治疗糖尿病吗
to know that it helps diabetes?
对  我觉得她应该试试
Yes. I think she should.
惊不惊喜  那医生是个女人
Surprise! The doctor's a woman.
这是性别歧视
Sexist!
没错
Oh, yeah.
-说得好  -就是性别歧视
- Good point. - That is sexist.
我不介意抽大麻
Look, I don't have a problem with pot.
我可以随时开始抽
I can start any time I want.
我现在就来点
I'll do some right now.
太好了  "宁静"
Perfect. "Serenity."
看见了吗  没事
See? Nothing.
我可能是对它没反应的人之一
I'm probably one of those people it doesn't work on.
我感觉我像是在一部
I feel like I'm on an elevator
同时升降的电梯上
that's going up and down at the same time.
这不对劲  你说过这是健康产品
Something's wrong. You said this was about wellness,
但我感觉嗨了
but I feel high.
好了  好了  听着
Okay, okay, listen.
你要明白的是
What you need to understand is this,
我也嗑嗨了
I'm high, too!
我宁静得不得了
I'm Serenityed out of my gourd.
没错  宝贝
Yeah, baby.
我得冷静下来  我得吃点东西
I've got to come down. I've got to eat something.
那是鸡肉馅饼[大麻饼]
Um, that was a chicken pot pie.
不  我吃了可食用大麻制品
Oh, no. I ate an eatable.
你用大麻纸巾擦了嘴
And you just wiped your mouth with a Hash-nap,
这是最强劲的产品
the most potent thing here.
洗手间
我平时都是这么走路的吗
Is this how I always walk?
我的胳膊怎么摆  明白了  这很正常
What do I do with my arms? OK, got it, this is normal.
亲爱的  是我
Honey, it's me.
侯默
Homie.
你会没事的
You're gonna be okay.
就在两小时内  会像是12个小时
In two hours ‭that will seem like 12.
你真好
You're so sweet.
我却出卖了你
And I ratted you out.
没事  我明白的
No, I get it.
你找到了一个让自己感觉特别的位置
You found a place that made you feel special,
而你不想失去它
and you didn't want to lose that.
我还是觉得好怪异
I still feel weird.
可能我也怪异了  你就不会觉得那么怪异了
Maybe you'd feel less weird if I were weird, too.
来  我抽一根你的未来主义烟卷
Here, I'll smoke one of your futuristic joints.
那不是大麻烟
That's not a doobie!
大麻油  消炎药
极易燃
天啊  爸爸  你干了什么
Oh, man, Dad, what did you do?
大麻布料就像纸一样易燃
Hemp clothes burns like paper!
全错了  全错了  全错了
All wrong, all wrong, all wrong!
冷静一点
Be cool.
振作一点  没脖子
Cheer up, neck face.
我很确定的是  人生中充斥着痛苦
If there's one thing I know, it's life is nothing but pain.
人们总会需要你我这样的人
People will always need guys
让他们醉生梦死
like you and me to get them wasted.
多谢  幻觉中的怪物
Yeah, thanks, monster man hallucination.
你的话让我深感宽慰
Your words are a-a great comfort to me.
我们会想办法熬过去的
We'll get through it somehow.
我能和你们一起...
Well, can I come with y...
很好&非常好
关闭
针对发生在德里克豪宅的那场
In reaction to the destructive Drederick blaze
同时摧毁了手语猴子庇护所的大火
which also destroyed the Sign Language Monkey Sanctuary,
镇议会已通过了一项紧急法令
the town council has passed an emergency ordinance
取缔了大麻售卖
outlawing the sale of cannabis.
没了那笔税钱
Without that tax money,
阿麦的早教中心也得关了
Maggie's pre-education center will have to close.
他们在教她普通话
Aw, man, they were teaching her Mandarin.
这可能是最好的结局
Well, it's probably for the best.
尽管他们说某样东西没有成瘾性
Even though they say something's not addictive,
你还是会上瘾的
you can still get hooked.
你可不想那样
And you don't want that.